《致命弯道3：丧生》
好诶 好诶
Yeah! Yeah!
快 特里 快
Go,Trey! Go!
快点 你们太慢了
Come on,man! You guys are slow!
别被岩石卡住了 天啊
Don't get caught up in the rocks. Oh,my God!
快 保持南北方向
Come on. Keep it going north-south.
小心这块岩石
Look out for that rock!
小心
Look out!
喔 喔
Whoo! Whoo!
轮到我了
My turn.
就这样
That's it.
亚历克斯 没人对你说过刚进入瀑布的时候要慢点吗?
Jesus,Alex. Anyone ever told you to go slow when we first enter the chute?
胆小鬼才是
Slow is for pussies.
进去
Get in there.
我们就在这里扎营吧 好 我们把船拉进来
Let's set up camp here for the night. All right. Let's pull the boats in.
这地方太美了
This place is perfect.
嘿 我们去找些材火
Hey. We're gonna go look for some firewood.
你去嘛 我要抽两口
You do that. I'm gonna blow a stick.
别给老子都抽完了
Don't hog all the kush.
嗯
Mmm.
你真是个暴露狂
You are a total exhibitionist.
那又怎样? 女人的身体需要呼吸
So what? The girls need to breathe.
我们在树林深处 谁看得到?
We're in the middle ofthe woods. Who's gonna notice?
天晓得 说不定就有个弹琴的变态
I don't know. Some banjo-playing freak.
- 什么? - 算了吧.
- What? - Forget it.
特里呢?
Hey,where's Trey?
哦 这童子军正在河边捡材火
Oh,the Boy Scout's gathering the right kindling up the river.
好像那里的不太合适
Like there's a wrong kind.
我去找他
I'm gonna go look for him.
你们不要做出吓坏动物的事情
You guys,don't do anything that will scare the animals.
- OK? - 嗯
- Okay? - Mm-hmm.
嘿
Hey.
亚历克斯 说我放荡 你觉得我放荡吗?
Alex thinks I'm a slut. Do you think I'm a slut?
正是 但我就是喜欢你这点
Yes. But that is what I love about you.
- 我晓得你喜欢我的波波 - 就是 你有这么完美的大波
- I thought you loved my tits. - I do. You have perfect tits.
我能一直这么抓着
I could hold them forever.
救命
Please help me!
噢
Oh!
救命
Help!
来人啦 救命 救命
Please,help! Help!
噢
Ooh!
嘿 快来
Hey,come on!
给我滚开 光头佬?
Why don't you step off,skinhead?
对抗一个人 就是对抗整个团队?
You fight one bean,you fight the whole burrito,huh?
让开
Quita!
你安排好了?
You got your shit set?
只要别让你的人搞砸就行了
Just make sure your fucking tacojockeys don't fuck it up.
别来考验我 小子
Don't test me,cabron.
一般钱给少了 我会割你的喉咙
You know,normally,I'd slit your throat for less.
但我们是生意伙伴 就算了吧
But seeing as we're business partners,I think I'll let it slide.
记住
Just remember one thing.
你不是这里唯一擅长割喉咙的人
You're not the only one that's good at slitting throats.
我已经付了他妈足够多的钱来安排这事
Now,I paid you a lot offucking money to help put this together.
所以下周最好所有事情都能按照计划进行
So the shit better come good like clockwork next week.
别担心 查韦斯 我不会耍你
Don't you worry,Chavez. I won't burn you.
钱就是钱 钱能使世界运转
Money is money. It makes the world go round.
噢
Oh.
我可不担心
I'm not worried,
但我们都知道你经常把事情搞砸
but we all know how you like to burn things.
纵火犯
Firebug.
别停下来
All right,keep moving.
走
Let's go,guys.
他是个白痴
Man,he is an idiot.
我只是转述他的话
I'm just telling you what he told me.
嘿 最后一天还迟到?
Hey. Late on your last day?
法玛 可能会记录在你的考评上
Farmerwill probably write your ass up for it too.
随他怎么写
He can write all he wants.
奈特 这布料很高档啊
Damn,Nate,those are some expensive-looking threads.
成功还得靠衣着 瓦尔特.
You got to dress for success,Walter.
我刚告诉瓦尔特 法玛 说过…
Nate,I wasjust telling Walter here how Sergeant Farmer was saying...
你第一学期就要被勒令退学了
you're probablyjust gonna flunk out in your first semester anyway.
噢 谁在乎他怎么想
Oh! Nice. I really care what he thinks.
对了 监狱长找你 他说今晚有罪犯要转移
Ah,by the way,warden wants to see you. He says we got a transfer tonight.
哦 我只想稳稳当当上完班回家 不想外出
Oh,man,I just wanna have a peaceful shift and go home,not go on a goddamn road trip.
- 回头见 - 再见
- I'll see you out there,man. - See ya.
"A"… 区犯人离开院子
Cell Block "A"... prisoners,clear the yard.
离开院子
Clear the yard.
- 监狱长 你找我? - 奈特
- You wanted to see me,Warden? - Nate.
- 认识这位威利吧? - 是啊 三区的犯人
- You know Willy here,don't you? - A prisoner from Cell Block 3.
威利·华雷斯 其实是个警官 这是Marshal Davis 警官
WillyJuarez is actually U.S. Marshal WilliamJuarez. This is Marshal Davis.
他们帮助我们转移到黑泽尔顿
They're gonna help us out with the Hazelton transfer,
尤其是Carlo 查韦斯
specifically with Carlo Chavez.
应该是下星期转移吧
That transfer isn't supposed to happen until next week.
对 我提前到今晚了 我听到些消息…
Yeah,well,I pushed it to tonight. Our friends here got word...
查韦斯的团伙想在转移途中救他
that Chavez's gang may attempt to break him out during the transfer.
我们让Juarez卧底来调查谁为他传的话
We putJuarez undercover to try and find out who he's passing the information through.
你到车上把查韦斯跟他锁在一起
You chain him up next to Chavez on the bus.
奈特 我的真实身份只告诉了你以防意外
Nate,onlyyou will know my real identity in case ofan incident.
这个计划要成功 就要让查韦斯相信我
Now,for this to work,Chavez has to trust me.
保险起见 我改变了路线
As an added precaution,I've altered your route.
除了我们 没人知道
Nobody knows it but the people in this room.
靠你了 奈特
I'm counting on you,Nate.
- 谢谢 艾力 - 不客气 老大
- Thanks,Ally. - No problem,boss.
警务站 我是副手Lane
Sheriff's station. Deputy Lane speaking.
啥时候?
Yeah. When?
他们开的什么样的车?
What type ofvehicle were they driving?
好 我们到哪接你们?
Ye-Yeah. Where can we reach you?
谢谢 我们会联系你的
Thanks. We'll get back to you.
几个大学生失踪了 去河里划橡皮艇 再也没回来
Some college kids went missing. They were river rafting and didn't come back.
- 多久了? - 有几天了
- How long? - A couple ofdays.
- 哪里? - 蓝鱼河附近
- Where? - Bluefish River area.
可能是在那野营 想多嗨皮几天
They probably stayed over so they could camp a little longer.
- 我开车去看看 - 我去就行了 警长 你不用亲自去
- I'll take a drive out there. - I can do that,Sheriff. You don't have to.
没事
No. It's fine.
我想呼吸下新鲜空气
I could use the fresh air.
走 利昂
Come on,Leon!
快 嘿
Hey,come on! Hey!
- 你们他妈的想干什么? - 我们坐车出去兜兜风 查韦斯先生
- What the fuck do you want? - We're going on a bus ride,Mr. Chavez.
- 现在? - 是的 你知道该怎么做
- What,now? - Yeah,now. You know the drill.
- 这次转移不对 你们要带我去哪? - 黑泽尔顿
- Well,this shit ain't right. Where are you taking me? - Hazelton.
但是他们告诉我是下周转移
But they said I wasn't going till next week.
我猜有人迫不及待想爆你菊花了
I guess they couldn't wait to see you.
- 我东西咋办? - 我们会打包运走的 走吧 查韦斯
- What about my shit? - We'll have it boxed up and shipped. Let's move,Chavez.
再碰老子一下 就扭断你的手指
Touch me again,I'll break your fuckin' fingers.
快走吧 别逼我冒火
Just move your ass before I lose my patience.
哦 不 别把我和这个杀人犯锁在一起
Oh,no,you don't. No. You're not chaining that murderer next to me.
闭嘴 克劳福德.
Shut up,Crawford.
让查韦斯走前面 Juarez随后 其他人跟上
Let's get Chavez up front followed by Juarez here and then the rest of'em.
你有什么意见?
What's your problem?
我的意见是 我不想和一个疯子锁在一起…
My problem is I don't wanna be chained to a whackjob...
把战后的创伤都发泄在一个酒吧服务员身上
who went all post-traumatic stress on some poor asshole in a bar.
打 打… 打过仗又能怎么样呢 兵哥哥?
I mean,what-what-what... You know,couldn't hack the war,soldier boy? Huh?
- 喝点酒就控制不住了? - 我就推了他一下 他就摔倒了
- Can't handle your liquor? - Listen. I pushed the guy. He fell.
恰好撞到头部? 我是无辜的
And he hit his head. Okay? I'm innocent.
- 是啊 我也是 - 你们都是无辜的
- Yeah. So am I. - And so is everyone else in here.
永远不要相信囚犯 恩?
Never trust a con,huh?
我才不信你的狗屁话 当兵的
I'm not buying your bullshit,soldier boy.
我听说你抢劫取款机的时候被抓到了
I heard you had your hands all up in the cash register.
- 少来烦我 - 哦 兵哥哥希望不去烦他
- Just leave me alone. - Oh,now. Soldier boy wants to be left alone.
哦 她咋啦? 是不是你老婆背着你劈腿了?
Oh! She had what? You get a "DearJohn" letter?
是不是当你发现…
Yeah. Yeah,went psycho...
你老婆和海军陆战队员嘿咻的时候 精神崩溃了?
when you found out yourwife was fucking a real marine,you punk-ass bitch?
- 够了 闭嘴 - 我只是不想和杀人犯锁在一起
- That's enough. Shut up. - Man,I'm just saying,I don't wanna be chained to a murderer.
我至少是个偷车的 这是正当职业
I mean,at least stealing cars,that's an honorable trade.
老天 克劳福德 弗洛伊德 啥了三个我们知道的人
Jesus Christ,Crawford. Floyd over here killed three people that we know about.
- 这不一样 弗洛伊德是我的朋友 - 快走
- That-That's different,man. Floyd's my friend.  - Just get moving!
继续走
Keep it moving.
让开 注意你的步子
Get out ofthe way. Move. Watch your step.
这是中转站 在这里加油
Here are the transfers. Gas up here.
在你们预定到达时间之前20分钟会通知警长
The sheriffwill be told you're coming 20 minutes before you're scheduled to arrive.
草泥马的 让我们通宵赶路
Stupid shit,making us go all night.
马勒戈壁的 你说呢?
Fucking bullshit! Don't you think?
闭嘴 别他妈说话
Shut the fuck up and don't talk.
佛洛依德
Floyd!
- 干什么? - 你笑个J8?
- What the hell?  - What you laughing at,bitch?
- 去死吧 Adolf - 你死定了 墨西哥人
- Fuck you,Adolf. - You're dead,wetback.
好了
Enough!
你关心的不应该是他?
It's not him you should be worrying about. Right?
放心 我把话传出去了
It's all right. I got the word out.
最好别出什么差错 朋友
It better be all right,homes.
对了
So,
你念完法律之后干什么?
what you gonna do when you graduate law school?
做律师
Practice law.
这我知道 聪明人
I know that,wiseass.
- 哪种律师? - 能让我在曼哈顿东区…
- What kind of law? - The kind that buys me a big townhouse...
买一处大房子的律师
on the Upper East Side of Manhattan.
- 那么 你是为了钱? - 我计划做些免费服务
- So it's all about money? - I plan on doing some pro bono work.
但是我要先取得成功
But first I got to be successful.
你很有追求嘛
Hmm. You got some pretty big expectations.
我上完学 念完法律
I put myselfthrough school,and I'm gonna put myself through law school.
工作到退休 然后去迈阿密
And when I'm all done,I wanna retire to,like,Miami.
南沙滩 享受生活
South Beach. Live a nice,comfortable life,you know.
退休?
Retire?
到时候你都老的享受不鸟了
Man,you'll be too old to enjoy it.
钱不是万能的 兄弟
Money isn't everything,my friend.
- 我得吁吁 - 受不鸟了
- I gotta go. - Just can't wait.
- 走 - 老天
- Move. - Oh,God.
- 瓦尔特 急什么? - 我要小便
- Walter,where's the fire? - Man,I got to go.
嘿 我也是 你能不能快点?
Hey,hey,me too,man. Can you hurry it up?
你们挨个挨个去厕所
You will each have an opportunity to use the restroom.
- 继续走 - 嘿 美女
- Keep moving. - Hey,sweetie.
你是奈特? 奈特 威尔逊?
Nate? Nate Wilson?
- 真没想到 - 你好啊 警长
- Well,I'll be damned. - Hi,Sheriff.
上次看到你的时候你才12岁
I haven't seen you since you were about 12.
后面你们搬家了
Well,since your folks moved away.
这是利昂吗? 过来 伙计
Is that Leon? Here,boy.
是的 14岁了 还是很笨
Sure is. Fourteen years old and still acts like a knucklehead.
- 你爸怎么样了? - 几年前去世了
- How's your dad? - Uh,Dad passed away a few years back.
妈妈还很好
Mom's fine though.
- 抱歉 - 下一个
- I'm sorry to hear that. - Next.
他是个好人 以前在磨坊遇到麻烦…
He was a good man. He was a great help when we had that trouble...
- 他帮了我们很大的忙 - 嗯
- at the old mill years ago. - Mm-hmm.
恐怕就是那时留下的病根
I think it got to him.
真没想到你都这么大了
I can't believe howyou've grown.
而且成了法律工作者
Law enforcement to boot. Hmm.
- 你们认识? - 是啊 奈特就在这里长大的
- You two know each other? - Sure thing. Nate was brought up around here.
奈特 我就知道你是乡下人
Damn,Nate. I knewyou were a hick.
- 但不知道你在这么鸟不生蛋的地方长大 - 就是这
- But,like,shit,this is the middle of nowhere. - Yeah.
- 来点咖啡? - 好
- Coffee? - That'd be great.
好
Yeah.
你最好是在盯着我的胸牌看
That better be my name tag you're staring at.
宝贝 他们是常规配置吗?
Are those guns standard issue,baby?
你刚才说什么?
What did you just say?
轻点 美女
Easy there,honeypot.
你喜欢粗鲁点的?
Oh,you like the rough stuff,huh?
即使把我全身绑起来 我也能满足你
Hell,I can do that. Even all tied up,I can show a girl a good time.
- 你喜欢被绑起来吗? - 你是说五花大绑…
- You like being tied up? - You mean all hog-tied,bound and gagged...
- 动也不能动? - 就是这样 宝贝
- to where I can't move a muscle? - Aw,yeah. That's it,baby.
不 我不喜欢被绑起来
No. I don't like to be tied up.
别这样 甜心
Aw,now,don't be that way,sugar.
你 进去
You,get moving.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么
So,uh,
你们为什么要经过"绿蔷薇"?
Why are you going through Greenbrier?
重要犯人 路线要保密
High-profile prisoner. They wanted to keep the route confidential.
- 要走老磨房的路? - 是的
- You going by the old mill road? - Yeah. That's the plan.
到山那边就走高速公路
Until we hook up with the main highway on the other side ofthe mountain.
- 很高兴见到你 奈特 一路平安 - 谢谢 警长
- It's good to see you,Nate. Safe trip. - Thanks,Sheriff.
你们穿过山区之后给我个电话
Hey,hey. Give us a call when you get through the backcountry.
或给我你的手机号 我给你打
Or give me your cell,and I'll call you.
也许你回来的时候我们可以喝一杯
Maybe we can grab a beer on your way back.
好啊
Sounds good.
我觉得这是个阴谋
I think it's a conspiracy.
我意思是 世界银行掌握在12个混蛋手中…
I mean,the World Bank is owned by 12 motherfuckers...
他们操纵我们的生活
who run our lives.
就在我打算买房子的时候…
And they decide to put us into recession...
他们搞出了个经济危机
just when I'm about to buy a house.
就像迈克·道格拉斯的那部电影
You know,it's like that old Michael Douglas movie.
法院的12个法官…
You know,the one with the 12 judges...
违背司法公正?
that decide to hand out the wrong form ofjustice?
- 什么电影? - 大执法
- What was it again? - The Star Chamber.
对 就是
Yeah. Yeah,that's it.
世界银行就是大执法
Yeah,I mean,the World Bank is the fucking Star Chamber.
- 喂 - 咋回事?
- Hello. - What is it?
哪个SB在闪老子远光灯
There's some asshole blinking his high beam.
过去 混蛋
Go around,asshole!
他又慢下来了
Now he's slowing down.
- 你到底过不过去? - 冷静 不要减速
- Make up your mind,prick. - Just keep cool. Don't slow down.
他把车灯关了
Hejust shut off his lights.
按紧急措施 不要停车 这可能是一次越狱
All right,we're in an emergency procedure. Don't stop. This could be an escape attempt.
怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on?
打开无线电
Get on the radio now.
黑泽尔顿…
Uh,Hazelton...
黑泽尔顿 我是押送车
Uh,Hazelton,this is Custody Bus.
马勒戈壁的
Holy shit!
草泥马
Damn it.
黑泽尔顿 我是格拉芙顿的2号押送车
Uh,Hazelton,this is Custody Bus 2 from Grafton Penitentiary.
回话 完毕
Come in. Over. Come in. Over!
妈的
Oh,fuck!
嘿 警卫
Hey,guard! Come on!
放我们出来 我们要烧焦了 起来
Let us out! We're gonna fry! Come on! Get up!
别让我烧焦了
Hey,don't let me burn!
- 我不想被烧焦 - 当然
- Please,I don't wanna burn! - Of course.
没人想成为烧饼
Ofcourse the fucking torch doesn't wanna burn.
- 瓦尔特 - 快
- Walter! - Come on,man!
快让我们出来 我们要烧焦了
Please get us out of here! We're gonna burn!
所有人到车后面去
Everybody move to the back ofthe bus.
查韦斯 走 从后面出来 快
Chavez,move. We're getting out the back. Come on!
起来 快
Get up! Come on.
他妈的快起来
Get the fuck up.
老实点 不然我就杀了你
Now,don't be a hero,and we'll be cool.
- 明白? - 我把另外两人弄出来
- All right? - Let me get the other two out ofthe bus.
闭嘴 钥匙给我
Shut the fuck up and hand me the keys.
掉在车里面了
They're in the bus. I dropped them.
把枪放下 不然打爆你的头
Drop the gun,or I'll blowyour face off.
也许我应该帮监狱节省房间和伙食
Maybe I should just save the state the cost ofroom and board.
你们看见了吗? 正中脖子
You guys see that shit? Right in the fucking neck.
伙计们 快出来
Hey,guys,come on out!
你的白痴伙计差点把我们都害死了
Your idiots nearly killed us all.
怎么回事?
What the fuck was that?
打这个混蛋 快
Shoot the fucker! Come on!
谁在那边?
Who's out there?
在巴士爆炸之前 快走
Let's move before the bus blows. You,move.
- 瓦尔特还在车上 - 我可不管 走
- Walter's still on the bus. - I don't give a shit. Move.
快 我们走吧
Now! Come on. Let's get out ofhere.
我是乡下人 也没见过谁用弓箭的 是谁?
I know I'm a redneck,but a bow and fucking arrow? Who the fuck does that?
我不知道 我也不管
I don't know,and I don't give a shit.
我只知道我们要离开这里
All I know is we're all getting the fuck out of here.
你到车上 拿到铁链的钥匙
You,get in that bus. Get me the keys for these chains.
瓦尔特
Walter
来 我带你出来 快
Come on. I'm gonna get you out of here. Come on. I got you.
聪明
Smart move.
把他弄起来
Now,get him up.
继续走
Get going.
停下来 把这该死的脚链打开
Okay,let's stop here and get offthese fucking leg irons.
我靠 这钥匙是怎么回事?
Fuck. What's up with these keys?
有三套不同的钥匙
There are three different sets of keys.
分别是手铐 笼子和脚链
One for the cuffs,one for the cage and one for the leg irons.
- 那就给我其他的 - 在车里 我说过了
- So hand me the other ones. - They were in the bus. I told you.
- 我只找到这个 - 他撒谎 杀了他
- This is the only set I found. - Fucking liar. Kill him.
杀谁我说了算
I say who lives and who dies.
去你妈的
The fuckyou do,asshole.
我们先查清楚这是怎么回事吧
Let'sjust find out exactly what's going on around here. All right?
- 我们本来应该多久到黑泽尔顿? - 天亮之前
- When was Hazelton expecting us? - Just before dawn.
好吧 那我们还有5个小时的时间
All right. Now,that gives us a five-hour head start.
我们都戴着脚链 根本走不远
Man,we ain't going anywhere in a hurry all tethered together by the ankles like this.
对 我们得想个办法把脚链弄开
You're right. We have to find a way of getting out ofthese irons.
警长说你在这里长大的 我们该走哪条路?
You. Sheriffsaid you grew up around here. Which way do we go?
- 过了很多年了 我记不太清楚 - 把这个混蛋杀了吧
- It's been years. I don't know. - Just kill the son ofa bitch,man.
不 威尔逊警卫要做我的指南针
No,no,no,no. Officer Wilson here's gonna be my compass.
带我找到电话 我就不杀你
You take me to a phone,you live.
否则 就死
You don't,you die.
- 明白了吗? - 是的
- Do I make myselfclear? - Yeah.
- 好 - 袭击我们的人是怎么回事?
- Good. - What about whoever's out there?
他们识相的话是不敢回来的
They won't be coming back ifthey know what's good for them.
我们现在走哪条路?
Now,which way do we go?
在山顶附近有一个旧的护林员防火瞭望塔
There's an old forest ranger's fire watchtower near the top ofthe mountain.
应该会有通讯设备
It should have communication equipment.
- 无线电 手机 - 好
- A radio. Maybe a cell phone. - Good.
带上你的猪 然后带路
So pick up your pig and lead the way.
迈阿密 南沙滩 我应该在那个地方
Miami. South Beach. That's where I should be.
退休 还有一群美女
Retired and surrounded by pussy.
不错的计划
Sounds like a plan.
速度点
Hurry it up.
只要一有机会 你就杀了这傻逼 听见了吗?
You kill that motherfucker first chance you get. You hear me?
听到了 你省点力气吧
I hearyou,Walter. Save your energy.
他在那
There he is!
蛋定
Take it easy.
- 别激动 没人要伤害你 - 是他们的人?
- Take it easy. Nobody wants to hurt you. - Is that one of'em?
- 就是这个婊子干的? - 别傻了
- A fucking little bitch did all this? - Don't be stupid.
她不是我看见的拖车上的人 跟她没关系
She's not who I saw on the tow truck. She's got nothing to do with this.
- 我们杀了这个女人继续走吧 - 你不会有事的
- Let'sjust cap the bitch and move on. - You're gonna be fine.
也许我们该把她OOXX了
Maybe we should fuck her first.
我不了解你 但是我很久没开荤了
I don't know about you,but it's been a long time.
你是谁? 到这里干什么?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
放我走 别让它找到我
Just let me go before it finds me.
- 求你了 - 让她走 我们不需要他
- Please. - Just let her go. We don't need her.
- 闭嘴 混蛋 - 谁也不能走
- Just shut up,asshole. - Nobody's going anywhere.
你出什么事了?
What happened to you?
我和朋友们两天前在蓝鱼河上…
My friends and I were rafting on the Bluefish River...
划橡皮艇
two days ago.
我们玩的很高兴
We were having a good time.
我们留下来过夜 事情就发生了
We stopped for the night. Then it happened.
- 什么? - 它杀了我的朋友
- What? - It killed my friends.
"它"? 我还以为是山里人
"It"? I thought it was just some hillbilly.
它要吃人
It eats people.
不 你肯定是糊涂了
No. You got to be out ofyour mind.
它是个畸形变异人
It's a fucking mutant! Deformed!
一只手上只有三个指头 杀人吃
It's got,like,three fingers on one hand. And it kills to feed.
我看到了
I've seen it.
那么 它为什么不吃森林里的动物?
So then,why doesn't it eat the animals in the woods?
因为这里没有动物 我们就是它的食物
Because there are none. It's a cannibal. We're its food.
我们带你离开
We're gonna get you out ofhere.
不会有事的 你叫什么名字?
Everything's gonna be okay. What's your name?
- 亚历克斯 - 我是 奈特.
- Alex. - I'm Nate.
看来你处境也不太好 是吧?
Looks like you're screwed too,aren't you,Nate?
你刚才说橡皮艇?
Did you just say rafts?
是的 两个
Yeah. Two of'em.
那么我们就坐橡皮艇走
Then that's our way out of here.
到河下游去
Down the river.
你带我们去 甜心 我会报答你的
Now,you take us there,sugar tits,and I'll make it worth yourwhile.
我宁愿和怪物在一起
I think I was better off with that freak.
走 走
Now move. Move!
喂 你觉得她多大了?
Hey. How old do you think she is?
不清楚 20岁吧
I don't know,man. Twenty maybe.
我真想把她给OOXX了
Goddamn it. I think I'm gonna make that one sit and spin.
我第一个来
Man,not if I don't first.
宝贝 你喜欢… 车车么?
Hey,baby. Baby. Hey,you like...you like cars?
你喜欢什么样的车 我就能给你偷到什么样的车
I can jackyou any car your sweet little ass wants.
嗯? 吖
Huh? Aw.
你们看
Well,would you look at that.
弗洛伊德,去看看 这是装甲车吗?
Hey,Floyd,check it out. Is that an armored car?
哪边?
Which way?
我不太清楚
I'm not sure.
我认为是这条
I thought it was this way.
但是看起来又不熟
But it doesn't look familiar.
小心
Careful.
你觉得这辆车有多少年了?
You. How old would you say that thing is?
起码50多年了
Late '50s maybe.
走
Let's go.
还是锁着的
Still locked.
- 爬到驾驶室看看 - 我们这是在浪费时间
- Climb in the cab and take a look around. - We're wasting valuable time.
- 走 - 他是对的
- Let'sjust go. - He's right.
我们走吧
Let's go.
闭嘴 给我老实点
Shut the fuck up,bitch,and don't even think about giving me an attitude.
否则马上杀了你 听见了吗?
'Cause I'll shoot you where you stand,you hear?
你 我让你爬到驾驶室去看看
You. I said climb in the fucking cab and take a look around.
- 有尸体吗? - 不 人都走了
- Any dead bodies? - No. They're gone.
肯定被弹出来了 我们去找找骨头
They must have been ejected. You guys have a look around for bones.
其中有个警卫肯定有钥匙
One ofthe guards must have had some keys.
我觉得你们什么都找不到
I don't think you'll find anything.
为什么?
Why?
因为有人从外面打碎玻璃爬了进来
Because somebody broke the windshield from the outside to get inside.
玻璃都在里面
All the glass is in here.
从这里的血迹来看 他们是死在车里的
And judging from the amount ofdried blood,they died in the cab.
- 还找到其他东西吗? - 没
- You find anything else? - No.
那就出来
Then get out ofthere.
发现了这个
Found these.
今天肯定是我们的幸运日
This mightjust be our lucky day.
真没想到
Well,I'll be damned.
我的春哥啊
Sweet Mother ofJesus!
- 我们发财了 - 我操
- We're fucking rich! - Holy shit!
- 你觉得这里有多少钱? - 管他的
- How much money do you think's in there? - Who cares?
- 这只会让我们更慢 - 那我们就平分你那一份
- It'll just slow us down. - Fine. We'll split your share.
- 你说平分 - 在哪里都是平分
- The fuck we will. - It's equal shares all around.
我凭什么要给你小子一份?
Why would I give a little fucking beaner like you anything?
他不会怀疑你的
He won't suspect you.
你们这些SB
You fucking morons.
一点小钱就让你们糊涂了?
A little money,and you all lose your mind?
这个样子做
This is how it's gonna work.
每人拿两个袋子
Each ofyou will carry two bags.
- 你 分袋子 - 我不想要钱
- You. Hand out the bags. - I don't want the money.
我不管你要不要钱 你必须带着 明白了吗?
I don't give a shit what you want. You're carrying the cash. Got it?
- 你也是 - 我得帮助瓦尔特 他一个人走不了
- You too. - I have to help Walter. He can't walk on his own.
我不管你要干什么 拿着袋子
I don't give a shit what you got to do. Pick up the bags.
来吧
Go on. Go on.
走 走
Now move. Move!
走吧
Go on.
- 他也要拿 - 他不行 伤得太重了
- Him too. - He can't. He's too badly injured.
- 我帮他拿 - 或者我来
- I'll carry his bags. - Or I will.
每个人都要带上自己的一份
Everybody's got to carry their own weight.
- 捡起来 - 拜托了
- Now,pick 'em up. - Please.
- 我来帮瓦尔特拿袋子吧 - 闭嘴
- Just let me carry the bags for Walter. - Shut up!
我等着呢
I'm waiting.
笑锤子
You smiling bastard.
捡起来
Pick 'em up.
Pick 'em up!
你知道关于钱 人们是怎么说的吗?
You know what they say about money,don't you,Chavez?
我不知道 警卫
I don't know,Corrections Officer.
怎么说的?
What do they say about money?
人们说 死人的钱再多…
They say money's hard to spend...
也花不出去
when you're dead.
你干了多愚蠢的事情? 不是么?
Now,that was a stupid thing to do,now,wasn't it? Huh?
给我把袋子捡起来
Nowjust pick up the bags.
捡你麻痹的
Shove it up your ass.
嗯 好吧
Uh-huh. Mm-hmm. Okay.
听到了吗? 捡你马勒戈壁的 草泥马
You hear me? Shove it up your ass,motherfucker.
天
Oh,my God!
不 瓦尔特 瓦尔特
No! Walter! Walter!
别这么做 现在不行
Don't. Don't do it. Not now.
让你牛B
You stubborn fuck.
这啥东西?
What the fuck?
过来
Come here.
就是这家伙暗算我们的? 一个变异孩子?
This is what's been fucking with us? A mutant kid?
这不是它
That's not him.
它是个成年人
This thing was a full-grown man.
同样是畸形
He was deformed like him.
看 有三个脚趾 可能是它的孩子?
Oh,would you look at that. It's got three fucking toes. Probably his kid,huh?
好
Okay.
我们给这山里人送个信
Now,let's send this cocksucking hillbilly a message.
拿着这个
You. Hold it.
- 弗洛伊德 - 什么
- Floyd. - Yeah.
- 把他按住 - 过来
- Hold him down. - Come here.
按住他
Hold him down.
- 橡皮艇在这 - 什么?
- Here's the rafts. - What?
这是双人皮艇
That's a two-man raft.
装不下我们和钱
That's not gonna hold all of us and the money.
- 嗯? 那我们怎么办? - 这只是装钱用的
- Huh? So what do we do know? - It'sjust for the bags.
你别想你能全都带走
You can go fuck yourself ifyou thinkyou're taking it all.
我们先把铁链去掉再说吧
Let's worry about that once we get these chains off.
这样不行啊
Man,that ain't gonna work.
可能这会有点痛
This might sting a little at first.
我靠… 草泥马
God... damn it! Fuck!
你为什么这么做?
What the fuck did you do that for?
你自己说的 石头不管用
Well,you said the rocks weren't gonna work.
- 我觉得这样能行 - 你他妈的疯了吗?
- So I thought that'll do the trick. - Are you fucking crazy?
我不知道 可能吧
I don't know. Maybe I am.
我们怎么安排橡皮艇?
How are we gonna deal with the boat?
先把它弄到河里
Let'sjust get it in the river first,
然后就会有办法了?
and then we'll figure it all out,all right?
- 我觉得这不是什么好主意 - 闭嘴 克劳福德
- Uh,I don't think that's a good idea,man. - Shut up,Crawford.
- 现在我们要走路了 - 你这婊子养的
- Now we're walking. - You stupid son ofa bitch!
我的天
Oh,God!
混蛋 你为什么要这么做?
Fuckin' asshole! Why did you fuckin' do that? Huh?
为什么这么做? 说话呀 他奶奶的说呀
Why did you fuckin' do that? Tell me! Fuckin' tell me!
住手
Stop it! Stop it!
你有什么要说的吗?
You got something to say? Huh?
你他妈还有什么要说的吗?
You got something to fucking say?
看来你还需要我这只骡子来抗你的钱了
Looks like you still need this mule to carry your money.
对 看来还要麻烦你了 威尔逊警卫
That's right. Then I guess it's back to you,Corrections Officer Wilson.
你想活命 就带我离开这里
Now,you wanna live,you get me the fuck out of here.
带路 带路
Now,lead on! Lead on!
起来 起来
Get up! Get up!
把它给我
Give me that.
走 走
Now,move! Move!
快走
Get a fucking move on.
听起来他已经知道教训了
Sounds like he's learned his lesson.
或者我们把它惹火了
Either that,or we just pissed him off.
晚上好
Good evening.
- Hello - 你好警长 我刚接到Cliff Moore的电话
- Hello. - Hi,Sheriff. I just got a call from a Cliff Moore.
他说昨天在河上游看到一辆卡车
He said he spotted a truck up by the upper river inlet yesterday.
- 看见那几个孩子了吗? - 没有
- Any sign ofthe kids? - No.
如果你同意 我想去看看
If it's all the same to you,I thought I'd drive out there and take a look.
- 有没有奈特 威尔逊和另外一个警卫的消息? - 还没有
- Any word from Nate Wilson or the corrections office? - No. Not a peep.
怎么了? 你在等电话?
Why? Were you expecting a call?
没什么 我有点不好的预感
No. I just got a bad feeling,that's all.
我很快就来
I'll be there in a minute.
这是什么?
What is that?
不可能 不过看来像是Preslow的钥匙
It can't be,but it looks like Preslow's keys.
很好 现在我们就能把脚链弄掉了
Good. Now we can get these fuckin' chains off.
趁现在
Now!
来啊 混蛋山里人 过来抓我啊
Come on,you motherfuckin' hillbilly! Come get me!
你想死么?
You got a death wish?
别再惹我 知道吗?
Don't fuck with me again. Right?
我草
Fuck.
这是怎么回事?
What the hell is going on?
我告诉你怎么回事
I'll tell you what's going on.
- 他要杀了我们所有的人 - 他在猎杀我们
- He's gonna kill us all. That's what's going on. - He's hunting us.
再过几个小时 就不只是他一个人对付我们了
Well,he won't be the only one hunting us in a couple ofhours.
- 我们走吧 - 我们怎么走
- So let's go. - How are we supposed to do that?
这里 切断膝关节
Here. Cut it at the kneejoint.
就不用切断骨头了
You don't have to cut through any bone.
- 天啊 - 胆小鬼 给我
- Jesus fucking Christ. - Fucking pussy. Give me that.
没用的墨西哥人
Fucking wetback.
膝关节 对
At the kneejoint. That's it.
混蛋
Piece ofshit.
好了 我们走
Okay. Let's get out of here.
拿起包 我们走吧
Come on. Get your bags. Let's get out of here.
拿着 快走
Take that. Come on! Move!
为什么不给黑泽尔顿监狱打个电话?
Why don't you call Hazelton?
说什么?
And say what exactly?
说我有不祥的预感? 奈特没有接我的电话?
That I got a bad feeling? That Nate didn't answer his cell?
就因为预感 不值得去看吧
Itjust seems like an awful lot ofeffort for a hunch.
这是我的预感 就让我去看看吧
Well,it's my hunch,so it's my effort.
你觉得他们逃走了?
You really think they staged a breakout?
我不知道 艾力
I don't know what to think,Ally.
河边的那辆卡车呢?
What about that truck up by the river?
你去调查
You follow it up.
这什么地方?
What is this place?
看起来不像是瞭望塔
This doesn't look like the watchtower.
不 我从来没见过这地方
It's not. I've never seen this place before.
肯定有什么工具来弄断铁链
There has to be some tools that we can use on these chains.
- 你最好搞快点 - 走
- And you better make it quick. - Move.
有工具
Jackpot!
- 给我 - 等轮到你 混蛋
- Give me that. - Wait your turn,asshole.
- 还有多远? - 我不知道
- How much farther? - I'm not sure.
- 也许一两个小时 - 你最好找到
- A couple of hours maybe. - You better find it.
我要找块面包吃
Oh-ho-ho,man. I got to go pinch a loaf.
- 我们分头走吧 - 不
- I say we split up. - No.
- 也许这是个好主意 - 你觉得需要投票吗?
- Maybe it's a good idea. - You think this is a democracy?
- 你想和我狡辩? - 你的人找到你之后又怎么样呢
- You wanna fuckin' debate me? - What happens when we meet up with your men?
那到时候你会干什么 查韦斯?
What are you gonna do then,Chavez?
盗亦有道?
What ever happened to honor among thieves?
你会杀了我们所有的人 把钱独吞了
You're gonna kill us all,then you're gonna take the cash foryourself.
- 你会这么做 - 你说的对
- That's what you're gonna do. - Yeah,you're right.
我可能会杀了你们
I probably will kill all ofyou.
- 那我干脆现在就杀了你 - 祝你好运
- Then why shouldn't we kill you now,eh? - Good luck.
你最好下手快点 否则你必死无疑
And you better be quick,oryou're surely gonna be dead.
然后我就杀了你们所有人
Then I'll kill all you motherfuckers.
但我觉得这不是你最好的选择
But I don't think that's in your best interest,
- 你最好妥协 - 嘿
- compared to a compromise. - Hey. Hey.
我刚用一百元擦了屁股
I just wiped my ass with a $100 bill.
从你那一份里扣 给我闭嘴
It's comin' out ofyour share,asshole. Now,shut the fuck up.
- 你有什么好建议? - 你有一把枪 而我有两把
- What do you propose? - You got one gun. I got two.
其他人没有
These humps have none.
我一人拿不了这么多的钱
Now,I can't carry all the bags ofcash on my own.
如果你杀了我 你也少了一个帮你的人
And ifyou kill me,that's one less pair of hands.
而且我还有你不具备的
Plus I have something none ofyou do.
- 哦? 什么? - 设施
- Yeah? What's that? - Infrastructure.
什么?
What?
我的人会找到我
My men will find me.
你可以跟我到藏身处 不用再逃亡
And all ofyou can come with us to a safe house and not be on the run.
作为交换 你们把一袋钱给我
And in exchange for that,you give me one ofthe bags you're all carrying,
剩下的一袋你自己留着
and you all get to keep the other one.
你怎么能相信他 弗洛伊德?
How can you trust him,Floyd?
不能相信
We can't.
成交
Deal.
那就走吧
Now get this bum up.
你朋友的事 很抱歉
Sorry about your friends.
这样下去不会有好结果
This isn't going to end well.
- 我知道 - 那你怎么跟他们站在一边?
- I know that. - Then why are you going along with them?
在这之前 我们锁在一起的
Up to now,being all chained together,
我没有其他选择 不是吗
I really didn't have much ofa choice,did I?
在这两个小时内 我们已经是第四次经过这棵树了
So that's the fourth time we've passed that tree in the last two hours.
你有什么打算 奈特?
What are you up to,Nate?
等待时机
Bidin' my time.
查韦斯 发现了 他会杀了你
Chavez catches on,man,he'll kill you.
他是对的 奈特 我都注意到了 你要小心
He's right,Nate. Even I noticed. You gotta be careful.
你应该回到路上 警察来的时候就自首
You should go back to the road. Turn yourself in when the police arrive.
我不能一个人穿过树林 没有武器
I am not going back through the woods alone,unarmed,
我会被那个怪胎杀掉
to get sliced up by that hillbilly freak.
他和查韦斯… 一样危险
I don't know who's worse... him or Chavez.
听着
Listen.
等我们到达瞭望塔 我会尽量帮你
I'll do what I can to help you once we've reached the ranger station.
谢谢 但你应该首先自己小心
I appreciate that,but I thinkyou should look afteryourselffirst.
用不着的人 查韦斯是不会带上一起走的
Chavez isn't gonna bring anyone along for the ride that he can't use.
你说得对
You're damn right.
他会为了钱把我们都杀了
He'll kill us all for the money.
如果没被食人族先吃了的话
Ifthat cannibal freak doesn't beat him to it.
真是讽刺
It's ironic.
- 什么? - 钱
- What is? - Money.
我努力一辈子上完学…
I struggled my whole life to put myselfthrough school...
- 然后离开这里赚钱 - 如何?
- so I could get out of here and make good money. - So?
现在我手上拿的钱比许多人一辈子挣得都多
Now I'm holding in my hands more money than most people ever make in a lifetime,
而我只想把它扔掉
and all I wanna do is get rid of it.
这是运木材的路 防火瞭望塔…
This is a logging access road. Fire watchtower's on the other side...
- 在山的另一边 - 等下
- further along the mountain. - Hang on. Hang on.
等一下 克劳福德
Hang on. Hang on. Crawford.
过来
Come here.
- 你能弄开那辆车吗? - 小菜一碟
- Thinkyou can jack that thing? - Piece ofcake,man.
终于有辆车可以带我们离开了
Finally,a ride out ofthis shit-hole.
等等 这是把我们撞到路边的那辆拖车
Wait a minute. That's the tow truck that ran us offthe road.
所以才让克劳福德 帮我们搞到手
That's why Crawford here is gonna go get it for us.
- 对不? 克劳福德? - 我不知道 我说…
- Right,Crawford? - I don't know about that,man. I mean...
就是辆卡车 过去看看就是了
It's a truck.Just run over there and check it out.
快 我们有钱了 现在我们离开这鬼地方
Come on! We got the cash. Now let's get the hell out of here!
不 让当兵的去
No way,man! Send soldier boy,damn it!
我不是偷车贼 你才是
I'm not the car thief. You are.
可能是个陷阱
Could be a trap,man.
快过去 混蛋
Get movin',asshole. Go on.
妈的
Damn it.
救命
Help me! Please!
该死的怪胎
Fuckin' hillbilly motherfucker!
我要找到你 然后杀了你
I'm gonna find you,then I'm gonna fuckin' kill you!
不
No!
我们原路返回 尽快离开这里
Let's backtrack and get as far away from here as possible.
他要杀光我们才罢手
He's not gonna stop until we're all dead.
- 这他妈的是谁? 告诉我 - 我不知道
- Who the fuck is he? Tell me right now! - I don't know!
你不知道 你是在这里长大的 警长说过
The fuckyou don't! You grew up here! The sheriffsaid so!
你最好在这个怪物回来之前带我们离开这里
Now you better get us the fuck out of here before that freak comes back.
操他妈的 我们不需要他了
Fuck him. We don't need him anymore.
杀了我 你们就要靠自己了
You kill me,and you're on your own... lost.
- 我不管 - 他什么都不知道 你看不出来吗?
- Maybe I don't give a shit. - He doesn't know anything! Can't you see  that?
喔 等等 如果现在杀了他 我们也完了
Whoa! Just wait a minute. If you kill him now,we are fucked.
好么? 我们不知道怎么走
Okay? We have no idea where we're going,
还有个怪物要把我们都干掉
with some crazy hick out there trying to pick us all offone by one.
不
No.
够了 走吧
Enough. Come on.
别再惹我生气
Now,you don't want to see me angry.
你带我去瞭望塔… 找到电话 听见了?
Now,you get me to that station... and a phone,you hear?
不
No!
停下 天啊
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! God!
我要休息
I need a rest.
给我起来 接着走
Get the fuck up. We gotta keep moving.
起来 你们两个
Get up,both ofyou.
- 带着钱我们走的慢 我们最好扔掉 - 不行
- It's the money that's slowing us down. We gotta lose it. - No way.
他们两个小时之后就会找到我们
They'll be looking for us in a couple of hours.
如果我们没到黑泽尔顿 FBI 联邦警察局…
Ifwe don't show up at Hazelton,the F.B.I.,U.S. Marshals...
所有西佛吉尼亚的警察都会追捕你
and every law officer in West Virginia is gonna be hunting you.
布兰登说得对 要想逃 就搞快点
Brandon's right. Ifyou want to get away,you need to move quicker.
- 把钱扔了 - 听我说
- Dump the money. - Now you listen to me.
要么我们带着钱走 要么在这里等死
We move now with the cash,or we all wait here and die.
是她拖了我们后退
She's the one who's slowin' us down.
啊
Ah.
别激动
Be cool.
不过她长的很正点
She's a nice piece ofass though.
我们把她给干了 再一枪杀了她…
Let'sjust pass her around,then pop her in the head...
然后走人…
and get the fuck out of...
我要杀了你 你这个贱人
I'm gonna kill you,you fuckin' bitch!
现在不行
Notjust yet.
蛋定
Now be cool. Stay calm.
我有枪
I got this in hand.
别激动?
Be cool. All right?
冷静一下
Now,you just chill the fuck out.
- 你死定了 臭婊子 - 我们都死定了 婊子养的
- You're dead,bitch. - We're all dead,asshole!
把枪还来
Give me my gun back.
看来你很容易冲动啊 弗洛伊德
Looks like you got some impulse-control issues there,Floyd.
我可不会给你
I don't think so.
如果怪物出来 三把枪都在你手上可不是什么好事
You having all three guns does us no good ifthat freak comes after us again.
我愿意冒险
Then that'sjust a chance I'm gonna have to take.
他们很快就能找到我们 明早就会全面搜查
They're gonna start lookin' for us soon. There'll be a full search by morning.
- 如果我们能坚持到那个时候 - 我们会的
- Ifwe make it till then. - We'll make it.
这些人好像不会轻易让你走
These guys don't look like they'rejust gonna let you go.
他们为什么还没杀你?
Why haven't they killed you already?
- 他们需要我 - 如果不再需要了呢?
- They need me. - And what happens when they don't need you anymore?
我可不希望到这一步 瞭望塔里应该有无线电和手机
I'm not planning on finding out. There should be a radio and cell phone at the watchtower.
到了之后我就呼救
I'll call for help once we get there.
- 这个计划能行得通吗? - 那有个梯子
- How do you plan on keeping this lot under control? - There's a ladder.
每次只能爬上去一个人
Only one person can climb up at a time.
75英尺高 还要经过一个活动门
It's 75 feet straight up and through a trapdoor.
每个瞭望塔都藏有把枪 我知道放在哪里
Each station has a gun hidden in it,and I know where they keep it.
那里空间很小 我们上去之后就能伏击查韦斯
It's a tight space. I can ambush Chavez when we're up there.
我只想回家
I just want to go home.
会好起来的 亚历克斯 我会带你脱身
It'll be okay,Alex. I'll get you out ofthis.
你走路有点慢啊 弗洛伊德?
Walkin' a little slow there,aren't you,Floyd?
她把你伤得很重吗?
She hurt you that bad?
- 去死吧 婊子 - 啊…
- Die,bitch! - Wha...
快来
Come on.
卡弗警长呼叫Lane 请回话 完毕
SheriffCarver calling Deputy Lane. Come in. Over.
艾力 我是Calvin 回话 完毕
Ally,this is Calvin. Come in. Over.
县警务局 我是卡弗警长
County Dispatch,this is SheriffCarver.
- 我想报告一起情况 完毕 - 请讲 警长
- I want to report an emergency. Over. - Go,Sheriff.
格拉芙顿监狱的押送车出了车祸…
The custody bus from Grafton Penitentiary has crashed...
在老磨房路37号路标附近
offthe old mill road near mile marker 37.
我过去看看 完毕
I'm goin' in to take a look around. Carver out.
- 警务局 我是卡弗 - 请讲 警长
- Dispatch,this is Carver. - Come in,Sheriff.
车上没人 我去找找看
There is no one onboard. Gonna see if I can track them.
- 完毕 - 收到
- Carver out. - Roger that.
快 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
好了 停下 够了
All right. Stop. He's had enough.
够不够我说了算
I say when the Nazi bastard's had enough!
- 他们去哪条路了? - 我不知道
- Now,which way did they go? - I don't know.
我没看见他们去哪了
I didn't see 'em go.
来
Come on.
那我们怎么处置他?
Well,what do we do with him?
不管他
Fuck him. Leave him.
奈特 我…
Nate,I...
我跑不动了
I can't run anymore.
我… 得休息一下
I... I just need a minute.
我们要接着走
We need to keep moving.
只要再过几个小时 我们就安全了
Wejust have to make it a few more hours,and then we'll be fine.
警察就要来了 你能行的
The police are coming. You can do this.
听着 查韦斯
Listen,Chavez.
你一个人无法离开这里
You can't get out of here alone.
- 你也清楚? - 我有办法
- You know that,right? - I'll be fine.
- 我可以带你离开森林 - 你想要什么?
- Well,I can get you out ofthese woods. - So,what do you want?
公平的交易
A fair deal.
- 要多少钱? - 不
- How much? - No.
我不想要钱 我不需要
I don't want the money. I don't need it.
但你要保证你的人来了之后 你要让我走
But you gotta promise me that you'll let me go when your boys show up.
好
Fine.
另外 我也要一把枪
And,uh,I also need one ofthose guns.
为什么我要给你?
Why should I give you a gun?
因为追杀我们的人会一直追杀我们 直到死
Because whatever's hunting us is gonna continue hunting us till we're both dead.
这是简单的道理 两人有枪比一人有枪要好
It's simple tactical strategy. Two gunners are better than one.
我为什么要相信你?
And why should I trust you?
我为什么要整你?
Why would I fuckyou?
我帮你对付弗洛伊德了 是吧?
I helped you with Floyd,didn't I?
我刚才也没跑
Well,I didn't run.
啊
Ah.
你要带他们去哪 奈特?
Where will you take them,Nate?
我这把岁数已经跟不上了
I'm too old for this shit.
来
Come on.
我们得走了 我们走得还不够远
We gotta go. We're not far now.
快 我们要快走
Psst! We gotta move.
接着走
We gotta keep moving.
- 我已经走不动了 - 加油
- I can't go on anymore. - Come on.
在那里
Over there.
好 我们把袋子放这儿 来
Okay. Let's leave the bags down over here. Come on.
等会回来拿
We'll come back for them later.
你不应该跑的
You shouldn't have run.
住手 住手
Stop it! Stop it!
闭嘴 婊子
Shut the fuck up,puta!
这都是你的错
This is all your fault!
- 也许我该先杀了你 - 等等 这样不会有什么用处的
- Maybe I should end you first! - Wait. That's not gonna get us anywhere.
能让这婊子别再碍事
It gets the bitch out ofthe way though!
瞭望塔就在山的那边
The watchtower'sjust right over the hill.
你一晚上就带着我们绕圈子
You've been leading us in circles all night.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I believe you now?
就在山那边… 我发誓
It'sjust over the hill... right there. I swear.
- 只要两分钟就能看见了 - 让这个贱人走
- It'll take two minutes to find out. Please. - Get this bitch out!
走
Move.
就这个? 被烧焦的木炭?
This is it? A bunch offuckin' charcoal?
- 肯定被烧没了 - 不会吧
- It must've been burned down. - No shit.
现在怎么办?
So now what?
我不知道 我只知道这里有无线电
I don't know. This is the only place I knew ofthat had a radio.
你一直都在耍我 是不是?
You've been fuckin' with me the whole time,haven't you?
- 不 - 去死吧 你在撒谎
- No. - Fuck you. You're a liar!
他没有撒谎 奈特以为这里会有瞭望塔
He's not lying. Nate thought the tower was gonna be here.
我们本来打算在这里求救
We were gonna barricade ourselves in and call for help.
我们接着走吧 现在至少都3 4点了
Well,let'sjust keep moving,all right? It's gotta be at least 3:00 or 4:00 a.m. by now.
- 我们可以去东北方向 - 我受够你的狗屁谎言了
- We could go northeast. - I've had enough ofyour bullshit.
给我跪下
Get on your fuckin' knees!
- 他妈的给我跪下 - 过了河10英里远有个小镇
- Get on your fuckin' knees! - There's a small town 10 miles past the  river.
- 我带你去那儿 - 去你妈的 说再见吧 混蛋
- I'll take you there. - Fuckyou. Say good-bye,asshole.
- 想想吧 查韦斯 - 他就在这附近
- Think about this,Chavez. - He's out there.
什么?
What?
我能感觉的到
I can feel him.
他在跟踪我们 越来越近了
He's been following us. He's close.
呲
Shh.
我警告过你了
I warned you.
滚开 赶走这条疯狗
Get it off me! Get this fucking dog off me!
把枪放下
Drop the gun! Down,boy!
- 赶走这条狗 - 拿着他的枪 奈特
- Get the dog off me! - Take his guns,Nate.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
还好 警长 见到你真是太高兴了
I'm fine,Sheriff. Just really glad to see you.
你没接我的电话 我… 就来看看
When you didn't answer your cell,I... I came looking.
- 还有其他人在那边 - 有多少人?
- There are others out there. - How many?
不知道 至少有一个囚犯和一个变态的山里人
Don't know. At least one other prisoner and some freak hillbilly local.
山里人? 这不可能
Hillbilly? That can't be.
拜托了 带我们离开这里
Please. Let'sjust get out of here.
好的 我们快到上面去
Okay. Come on. Let's move it up there.
你 快点 起来
Hey,you,come on. Move your ass. Get up.
快 走
Come on! Move it!
给我快点 你这混蛋
Move it,you son ofa bitch! Move!
来吧 孩子
Come on,honey.
他来了 越来越近了
He's close. He's really close.
- 谁? - 他是个怪物
- Who is? - He's a fucking monster.
拜托 我只想回家
Please. Please. I just want to get home.
好吧 别… 别怕 孩子
Oh,all right.Just... Just calm down,little lady.
如果你觉得能不拿钱走出这个森林…
Ifyou thinkyou're moving out ofthis forest...
那就他妈的大错特错了
without going back for the cash,you're fuckin' wrong.
给我走
Now move. Move.
中大奖了
Jackpot.
查韦斯 你这个蠢货
Chavez,you stupid son ofa bitch.
这就是警长报告的车祸地点
This is where the sheriff reported the bus crash.
就这种地形中步行 他们应该就在这个范围里
On foot in this terrain,they should be within this perimeter.
我们从所有周边开始 向里搜索
I want it approached from all sides,and we'll work our way in.
空中支援什么时候能到?
When is the air support getting here?
他们已经起飞了 应该在一小时后之后到
They're in the air. They should be here within the hour.
先生们 那里有我们的一个人
Gentleman,we have a man out there.
要千万小心
I want all precautions taken.
- 出发 - 是
- Let's move. - Yes,sir.
- 我的包呢? - 你肯定放在这个地方了?
- Where's my bags? - Are you sure this was the spot?
就是这个地方 老子的钱呢?
Yes,this was the spot. Now where's my goddamn fuckin' money?
嗯? 弗洛伊德干的.
Huh? It's Floyd.
我要杀了那个混蛋
I'm gonna kill that motherfucker.
不 我要先活剥了他
No. I'm gonna skin him alive first,
然后再杀了他
then I'm gonna fucking kill him!
我操
Shit!
你… 你留在这里看住他们
You... You stay here and you guard them.
听见了吗? 不要走动
You hear? You don't move! Don't move!
终于教训这个混蛋了
That'll teach that motherfucker!
看看现在是谁赢了 你这墨西哥混蛋?
Who's laughin' now,you Mexican piece ofshit?
让我走吧 布兰登.
Let me go,Brandon.
不行
I can't.
对不起 如果放你走 他会杀了我的
I'm sorry. If I do,he'll kill me.
- 那让她走吧 - 我不会离开你的
- Then let her go. - I'm not leaving you.
我看见你了
I see you!
你这混蛋 你他妈死定了
You cocksucker! You're fuckin' dead!
草泥马 查韦斯
Fuck you,Chavez!
去捡吧 去捡起来吧
You can pick it up! You can pick it all up!
你他妈死定了
You're fuckin' dead!
- 去死 - 法克鱿
- Dead! - Fuckyou!
来
Come on.
给我出来 你这混蛋
Come on out,you hick motherfucker!
我空手就能杀了你
I'll kill you with my bare fuckin' hands!
我操 我的钱
Shit! My money!
天
My God.
我们现在怎么办?
What do we do now?
如果不反击我们就… 死定了
We die... if we don't start fighting back.
我们去那个小镇吧
Let's head towards that town!
快 走
Come on! Move! Let's go!
- 这肯定是个陷阱 - 但他为什么觉得会有用呢?
- It's gotta be a trap. - Yeah,but why would he think it'd work?
他到底想要什么?
What the fuck does he want?
你听见了吗? 你这混蛋
You hear that? You hick-ass motherfucker!
你想要什么?
What do you want? Huh?
告诉我 你个婊子养的 不可能是钱
Tell me,you son ofa bitch. Can't be the money.
你已经烧掉了 你想要什么?
You've already fuckin' burnt that! Huh? What do you want?
好 你想跟我玩玩?
Okay. You want to fuck with me? Huh?
- 过来 过来 - 你干什么?
- Come here. Come here. - What the hell are you doing?
来啊 混蛋 一命还一命
Come on,fuck-stick! Huh? A head for a head!
她在这儿 带走吧
There she is. Take hers.
来啊 混蛋 你不是想要吗?
Come on,you bastard! It's what you want,isn't it?
把这婊子带走吧
Take the bitch!
跑
Run.
步
No!
- 亚历克斯 - 奈特
- Alex!  - Nate!
- 亚历克斯 - 住手
- Alex! - Stop!
- 不 - 亚历克斯
- No! - Alex!
亚历克斯
Alex!
- 你这混蛋 我们要去救她 - 不
- You son of a bitch! We've got to go after her. - No.
他走了 她也走了 我们接着走
He's gone. She's gone. We're moving on.
- 我不能把她交给他 - 我说 我们走
- I'm gonna leave her to him. - I said,we're moving on.
带我们离开这儿
Now lead us out of here.
不
No.
这是我很早就应该做的
This is something I should have a long time ago,
你这笨蛋
you stupid son ofa bitch.
对不起 到现在才出手
Here. I'm sorry I let it go this far.
你准备怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
到那个镇上去
Try and reach that town.
祝你好运
Good luck.
把她救回来 奈特.
Get her back,Nate.
我们要不要把他杀了?
Should we kill him?
我不是杀人犯 布兰登 你也不是
I'm not a murderer,Brandon,and neither are you.
有人吗
Somebody!
救命
Help me!
让我走吧
Please let me go!
救命
Help me!
奈特 奈特
Nate! Nate!
救救我
Help me!
请放我走吧
Please let me go!
奈特
Nate!
救命啊
Please,somebody!
救命
Help me!
利昂 嘿 乖孩子
Leon. Hey,boy.
过来 过来
Come here,boy. Come here.
找到她 利昂 找到 亚历克斯 好吗?
Find her,Leon. Find Alex,okay?
去吧
Go,boy.
救命
Help me.
不
No!
你做了个错误的选择 当兵的
You made a bad choice,army boy.
喂 喂
Hey! Hey!
我在这儿
Here! I'm here!
喂
Hey!
你在这里
There you are.
我一直在找你
I've been looking foryou.
来吧 混蛋
Bring it,you motherfucker!
怎么了 你这变态怪物?
What's the matter,you cracker-ass fuckin' freak?
不知所措了吗?
Scared of losing your head?
就这样了?
Is that it,huh?
你就是你的本事?
That all you got?
现在你死定了
Now you're dead!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you now!
你死定了
You're dead.
天啊
God!
看起来我们扯平了
Looks like we're even.
混蛋
Puto.
妈的
Shit.
不是多么厉害嘛
Ain't so tough.
干得好
Yeah. Good boy.
- 他在哪儿? - 我不知道 快
- Where is he? - I don't know.Just hurry.
奈特 她已经死了
Nate,she's dead.
不
No!
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
是的
Yeah.
我们离开这鬼地方吧
Let's get out of here.
看
Look.
天快亮了
It's almost dawn.
我们熬过了今晚
We made it through the night.
谢谢你 奈特
Thank you,Nate,
谢谢你回来救我
for coming back for me.
天啊
Oh,my God!
我的天 奈特
Oh,God,Nate!
天啊
Oh,God.
拿枪
Get the shotgun!
奈特
Nate!
亚历克斯 亚历克斯
Alex! Alex!
我们快离开这儿 亚历克斯
We gotta get out of here. Alex!
- 是我 - 先救亚历克斯
- It's me. - Get Alex first.
我扶着你
I got you.
我的腿
My leg.
胳膊给我
Give me your arm.
没事了 他已经死了
It's okay. He's gone.
真有意思…
Funny...
那些钱…
All that money...
都化成灰烬了
up in flames.
你没杀那个服务员 是吧?
You really didn't kill that bartender,did you?
没有
No.
现在怎么办
So,now what?
我就说你死了
You didn't make it.
没人会去查一个死人
Nobody goes looking for a dead con.
你会为了我这么做?
You'd do that for me?
别惹麻烦
Just stay out oftrouble.
我会的
I will.
相信我
Trust me.
是他们吗?
Is it them?
迈阿密 南海滩
Miami,South Beach,
周围都是美女啊
surrounded by pussy.
我会想你的 瓦尔特
I'm gonna miss you,Walter.
就像我说的
Like I said,
永远别相信囚犯
never trust a con.